Fistful of Vengeance is a action, fantasy film directed by Roel Reiné.
A revenge mission becomes a fight to save the world from an ancient threat
when superpowered assassin Kai tracks a killer to Bangkok.
Kai Jin, played by Iko Uwais.
Lu Xin Lee, played by Lewis Tan.
Tommy Wah, played by Lawrence Kao.
Zama, played by Pearl Thusi.
Preeya, played by Francesca Corney.
Zan Hui, played by JuJu Chan.
Fistful of Vengeance is a 2022 American supernatural action thriller film directed by
Roel Reiné, and written by Cameron Litvack, Jessica Chou and Yalun Tu.
The film serves as a follow-up to the first season of the television series Wu Assassins, and stars Iko Uwais, Lewis
Tan, Lawrence Kao, Rhatha Phongam,  JuJu Chan, Pearl Thusi, Francesca Corney, Jason Tobin and Simon Kuke.
The film was released worldwide on February 17, 2022, on Netflix.